=======================================================
pftl-842 A Common Love
Words and Music by: Charles F. Brown
Copyright ⌐ 1974 by Word Music, Inc. (ASCAP), 65 Music Square West Nashville, TN 37203
All Rights Reserved  Made In The U.S.A.  International Copyright Secured  Used By Permission
 
pftl-018 All Praise to Our Redeeming Lord
Words: Charles Wesley
Music: Sylvanus B. Pond
 
Verse 1
All praise to our redeeming Lord,
Who joins us by His grace,
And bids us, each to each restored,
Together seek His face.
 
Verse 2
The gift which He on one bestows,
We all delight to prove,
The grace through every vessel flows
In purest streams of love.
 
Verse 3
He bids us build each other up;
And, gathered into one,
To our high calling's glorious hope,
We hand in hand go on.
 
Verse 4
We all partake the joy of one;
The common peace we feel:
A peace to worldly minds unknown,
A joy unspeakable.
 
Verse 5
And if our fellowship below
In Jesus be so sweet,
What height of rapture shall we know
When round His throne we meet!
 
=======================================================
pftl-619 Take Time To Be Holy
Words: William D. Longstaff
Music: George C. Stebbins
 
Verse 1
Take time to be holy,
Speak oft with thy Lord;  
Abide in Him always,
And feed on His word.  
Make friends of God's children;  
Help those who are weak,
Forgetting in nothing
His blessings to seek. 
 
Verse 2
Take time to be holy,
The world rushes on;  
Spend much time in secret
With Jesus alone.  
By looking to Jesus,
Like Him thou shalt be;  
Thy friends in thy conduct
His like-ness shall see.  
 
Verse 3
Take time to be holy,
Let Him be thy Guide;
And run not before Him,
Whatever betide;
In joy or in sorrow,
Still follow thy Lord;
And, looking to Jesus,
Still trust in His word.
 
Verse 4
Take time to be holy,
Be calm in thy soul;  
Each thought and each motive
Beneath His control.  
Thus led by His Spirit
To fountains of love,
Thou soon shall be fitted
For ser-vice above.  
 

=======================================================
pftl-275 I Love to Tell the Story
Words: Catherine Hankey
Music: William G. Fischer
 
Verse 1
I love to tell the story,
Of unseen things above,
Of Jesus and His glory,
Of Jesus and His love;  
I love to tell the story
Because I know 'tis true;  
It satisfies my longings
As nothing else can do.  
 
Chorus
I love to tell the story!  
'Twill be my theme in glory
To tell the old, old story
Of Jesus and His love.  
 
Verse 2
I love to tell the story:
More wonderful it seems
Than all the golden fancies
Of all my golden dreams;  
I love to tell the story:
It did so much for me;  
And that is just the reason
I tell it now to thee.  
 
Verse 3
I love to tell the story:
'Tis pleasant to repeat
What seems each time I tell it,
More wonderfully sweet;  
I love to tell the story,
For some have never heard
The message of salvation
From God's own holy Word.  
 
Verse 4
I love to tell the story,
For those who know it best
Seem hungering and thirsting
To hear it like the rest;  
And when, in scenes of glory,
I sing the new, new song,
'Twill be the old, old story
That I have loved so long.  
 
 
=======================================================
pftl-628 The Day Thou Gavest
Words: John Ellerton
Music: Clement C. Scholefield
 
Verse 1
The day Thou gavest, Lord, is ended,
The darkness falls at Thy behest;
To Thee our morning hymns ascended:
Thy praise shall hallow now our rest.
 
Verse 2
We thank Thee that Thy Church, unsleeping,
While earth rolls onward into light,
Through all the world her watch is keeping,
And rests not now by day or night.
 
Verse 3
The sun that bids us rest is waking
Our brethren æneath the western sky;
And hour by hour fresh lips are making
Thy wondrous doings heard on high.
 
Verse 4
So be it, Lord: Thy throne shall never,
Like earth's proud empires, pass away;
But stand and rule and grow forever,
Till all Thy creatures own Thy sway.
 

=======================================================
pftl-234 Higher Ground
Words by: Johnson Oatman
Music by: Charles H. Gabriel
 
Verse 1
I'm pressing on the upward way,
New heights I'm gaining every day;
Still praying as I onward bound,
"Lord, plant my feet on higher ground."
 
Chorus
Lord, lift me up and let me stand,
By faith, on heaven's tableland,
A higher plane than I have found;
Lord, plant my feet on higher ground.
 
Verse 2
My heart has no desire to stay
Where doubts arise and fears dismay;
Though some may dwell where these abound,
My prayer, my aim is higher ground.
 
Verse 3
I want to live above the world,
Though Satan's darts at me are hurled;
For faith has caught the joyful sound,
The song of saints on higher ground.
 
Verse 4
I want to scale the utmost height,
And catch a gleam of glory bright;
But still I'll pray till heaven I've found,
"Lord, lead me on to higher ground."
 
 
