
  pftl 093 Christ for the World We Sing / Cristo Al Mundo, Cantad
  pftl 551 Rescue the Perishing / Busca al Que Errado Va
  pftl 139 Far and Near [NEW]

  pftl 628 The Day Thou Gavest / Hoy Diste Se±or
* pftl 632 The Gospel Is for All / íId a toda naci≤n!
* pftl 572 Send the Light / Da la Luz

  pftl 340 Into Our Hands [NEW]
  pftl 381 Lord, Speak to Me / Hßblame, Dios
  pftl 387 Lead Me To Some Soul Today / LlΘvame A Una Alma Hoy

  pftl 587 Soul, a Savior Thou Art Needing / Necesitas Un Salvador


